不要告诉我是水表有毛病
Do not tell me about a defective meter.
那些没有关系的人
Those who do not have a connection,
他们的水表已经被拆下来了，放在办公室里
their DP meters have been removed and kept in the office.
而这些人也收到了账单，这账单怎么来的？
They have also received a bill. How?
难道我不知道发生了什么吗？
Don't I know what is happening?
对于那些你已经发出三十万卢比账单的人
To those whom you have sent a bill of 3 lakhs,
都应该有10-15万卢比的赔偿
there would be a settlement of 1 - 1.5 lakhs with them or not.
我们和公众生活在一起，所以我们知道一切
We live with the public so we know everything.
别以为你可以用技术细节来愚弄我
Don't think you can fool me by talking about technicalities.
就像你愚弄公众一样
Just as you fool the public.
主席先生，我查清了这些问题，并加以纠正
Sir, I am aware of these problems and have rectified it too.
你做了什么纠正？
What rectification have you done?
那么，为什么这种情况更加频繁了？
Then why are such cases so frequent?
这是怎么回事？
What is this?
你看到夏季或者四月的帐单了吗？
Have you seen the bill for the summer season? Of April?
你看到了吗? 看看
Have you seen them? Look at them.
你告诉我四月份在哪里耕作？
Tell me where does farming take place in April?
农民在一月和二月浇灌麦田
The farmer has peak in January and February
达到耕作高峰
when he waters the wheat fields
为什么与四月和五月相比，这些账单要多得多呢？
and why is the bill as compared to those months more in April and May?
我还要给你举别的例子吗？
How many cases should I show you?
这个季节的账单是2000美元，现在是8000美元
The bill in the season is 2000/- and now it is 8,000/-
错误出现2-4次，而不是200-400次
Mistakes occur 2-4 times and not 200-400 times.
我们已经更换了农民用的水表
That is why we have changed meters for farmers.
我所说的一切都是谎言
Whatever I am saying is a lie.
我所说的一切都是谎言吗？
Is whatever I am saying a lie?
不，先生，我不是说你在撒谎
No, sir. I am not saying that you are lying.
你怎么能说我在撒谎呢? 所有的数据都在这里
How can you say that I am lying? All the records are here with me.
我们正在努力，先生
We are trying sir.
不要努力，给我结果
Don't make efforts but show me the result.
所有这些账单都应付清
All these bills should be settled.
到下周，这个错误要得到修正
By next week the system should be rectified.
解散，谢谢
Dismiss. Thank you.
领导怎么了? 他以前是个很安静的人
What has happened to sir? He used to be such a quiet man.
他从德里回来就开始训斥每一个人
From the time he has come from Delhi he is reprimanding everyone.
我想可能有人在德里训斥过他
I think someone might have reprimanded him in Delhi.
不知道
I don't know?
哦，不... 等一下
Oh no...one second.
先生，你要和 ALC 开会，他是从 Haryana 来的
Sir, you have a meeting with ALC, who has come from Haryana.
告诉他6点见面，现在我们要去婆罗多布尔考察
Tell him that we will meet at 6. Now we will go on a tour to Bharatpur.
好的，谢谢
Okay, sir. Thank you.
米什拉先生，现在这条路应该已经修好了
Mr. Mishra, by now the road should have been made?
是的，先生
Yes sir.
你知道在8月15日之前
You know that before 15th August
附近所有的村庄都必须要通铁轨
all the nearby villages have to be connected with metal road.
你到底知不知道？
Do you have any idea or not?
加快速度
Increase the speed.
长官，我们正在增加人手
Sir, we are hiring more manpower.
我们一定提前完成这项工程
We will complete the project before time.
你好
Hello.
他怎么样了？
How is he?
他很伤心，话不多
He is sad. He is not talking much.
你过来，我们给他打打气
You come over and we will cheer him up.
哦，不... 好吧，我会去的，在叔叔的茶摊，对不对？
Oh no...okay, I will be there. At uncle's tea stall, right?
是的
Yes.
你还好吗？
Are you fine?
你一定很好，因为你已经通过了
You must be fine as you have cleared. Come.
我会去的
I'll be there.
叔叔，给大家沏上好的茶，就是你在发榜日做的那个
Uncle, make tea for all. The one you make on result day.
别管了，朋友们，如果你们不能通过也没关系
Leave it, friends. It is fine if you couldn't clear.
已经尽力了，这很重要
You gave your best and that is important.
每年都有这么多人不能通过UPSC
Every year so many people cannot crack UPSC.
那又怎样? 他们做别的事
So what? They do something else.
有些人成为了企业家
Some become entrepreneur
有些做社会工作，有些成为记者
some do social work and some become a journalist.
- 我们也要做点什么-别说了，格里
- We will also do something. - Leave it, Guri.
你在胡说些什么？
What nonsense are you talking about?
你说起来容易
It is easy for you to say it.
为什么对我来说很容易? 我自己也没通过
Why is it easy for me? Even I did not clear.
这是他最后一次机会了
So many of them did not clear. It was his last attempt.
他很好
He is fine.
我们是战士
We are fighters. We are fighters.
我们不会失去希望，生命还没有结束
We will not lose hope. Life has not ended.
记住，在生活中，只有不战斗的人才会失败
Remember that in life only he has failed who did not fight.
不是吗？
Isn't it?
我要回我的村子去
I am going back to my village.
回家务农
I will do farming there.
你呢？
What about you?
你父亲经营水泥生意，你去接手吧
Your father has a cement business. Go and manage it.
你在这儿干什么? 他已经老了
What are you doing here? He is getting old.
否则，你的弟弟将得到所有的财产
Otherwise, your younger brother will get all the property.
阿比拉什，你呢？
And Abhilash, you?
他没有工作，他辞职了
He does not have a job. He left his job.
没问题，你跟我到村子里去
No problem. You come with me to the village.
我们兄弟俩都去务农
We both brothers will do farming.
我们将驾驶拖拉机，实现绿色革命
We will ride tractor and bring about the green revolution.
我们将成为斯瓦米纳森
We will become Swaminathan.
格里！
Guri!
你在那耍什么聪明？
Why are you acting over smart?
你要去哪? 告诉他们
Where are you going? Tell them.
你还有两次机会，为什么要撒谎？
You still have two attempts left. Why are you lying?
- 你为什么反应过度?-这是在演哪出？
- Why are you overreacting? - What is this drama, buddy?
- 我只是在逗你开心-这是在逗你开心吗？
- I'm just cheering you up. - Is this cheering?
你在开心吗? 你在取笑我
Are you cheering up? You are making fun of me.
我要种田吗? 你要种田，混蛋
Will I do farming? You will do farming, rascal.
你应该对你还有机会心怀感激
Be thankful for quota that you are getting a chance.
否则，你甚至不值得拥有它
Otherwise, you do not even deserve it.
你有没有听说过你不配拥有机会？
Did you listen that you do not deserve it?
你听到了吗，还是我走近你说，你这个聋子！你不配
Did you listen or shall I come closer to you and say. You Deaf.
SK，恭喜你通过了预考
SK, congratulations on the prelims.
谢谢你
Thank you.
阿比拉什和格里在这里吗？
Were Abhilash and Guri here?
他们刚才在，但现在已经走了
They were here but now they have gone.
他们两人吵的很厉害
They both had a heated argument.
你知道古丽是半聋的吗？
Do you know Guri is partially deaf?
他掩饰起来了，你知道吗？
He hides his quota. Did you know that?
这就是他经常弯腰的原因
Okay, so that is why he used to bend and stand.
是的，我也注意到了
Yes, even I noticed that.
好的，再见
Okay, bye. See you.
再见
Bye.
该死！
Damn!
你知道我可能太自私了
You knew it was so personal to me.
我不想跟你说话，你走吧
I don't want to talk to you. Go from here.
只有 SK 和你知道我的秘密，你们为我保守了很长时间
Only SK and you knew. You could have kept quiet for some more time.
我没心情听你的童年创伤，你走吧
I am not in a mood to listen to your childhood trauma. You go from here.
接受你已经失败的事实，为什么你要把怒气发泄在我身上？
Accept that you have failed. Why are you venting out your anger on me?
我没有泄露你的秘密
I did not tell the password of your bank
只是说出了真相
but just said whatever the truth is.
我不需要任何人的同情
I do not want anyone's sympathy.
我也不需要你同情
I do not want yours as well.
- 你觉得我会在你家务农吗?-我开玩笑的
- Do you think I will do farming at your place? - I was joking.
我的事业完蛋了，这对你来说是个笑话吗？
Is it a joke for you that my career is finished?
什么已经结束了? 生活还没有结束
What has finished? Life has not finished.
除了 UPSC 没有别的事业了吗？
Isn't there any other career than UPSC?
那你为什么还要接着考呢? 我们去种田吧
Why are you giving the next attempt then? Let's go and do farming.
喂，SK
Yes, SK.
近来可好？
How are you?
我很好
I am fine.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
很好
Good.
你什么时候来德里？
When are you coming to Delhi?
哦，对了! 我不能去你那参加演讲了
Oh yes! I could not take the lecture at your coaching.
我会叫我的一个同僚去，他就在附近
I will send one of the my friend who is posted close by.
我不是问这个
I did not call for that.
我问你什么时候来
I was asking when you are coming.
那还有什么事吗？
So what else?
当年离开纳加尔，到现在的德里
When you left Rajinder Nagar and now from Delhi...
你和格里总是有矛盾
You always had a problem with Guri.
算了，别再提那些事了
Forget it. Don't start all that again.
听着，听着，兄弟..
Listen. Listen, brother...
你走之前为什么不见我？
Why didn't you meet me before going?
格里还跟你说了他婚礼的事情
And Guri also told about his marriage when the date is so close.
我在你们的生命中没有任何价值
I don't have any value in your lives.
你知道我们三个在学院里被称为三脚架吗？
Do you know we three were called a tripod in the college?
听着，SK
SK look,
当三脚架的两条腿都出了问题
when there is a problem with two legs of the tripod
那么平衡就会被破坏
then balance with the third leg automatically gets spoiled.
但是剩下的那一条腿仍然在努力，虽然只能支撑一点点
But that one leg is making efforts so just support a little.
这是不可能的
It cannot be done.
因为其他两条腿不能达到同一水平
Because the other two cannot come on the same level.
我真的落后了，兄弟
I really lagged behind, buddy.
被你们远远甩在后面
Really lagged behind.
在过去的四年里，我一直在教书
For the last 4 years, I am teaching
我的学生都很优秀
and my students have excelled.
朋友们从来没有问过我幸福与否
And friends did not ever ask about my well-being.
SK，如果你需要任何经济上的帮助，我可以..
SK, if you need any financial help then I can...
这就是你的问题，兄弟，这就是你的问题
This is your problem, buddy...this is your problem.
我不会参加他的婚礼，SK
I will not attend his wedding, SK.
我没有强迫你参加婚礼
I am not forcing you to attend the wedding.
三脚架的三条腿是相辅相成的
The three legs of tripod need each other.
只有这样，才是完美的
Only then it will become picture perfect.
我不需要任何人，SK
I do not need anyone, SK.
我们走吧，先生? 您和 ALC 有个会议，先生
Shall we leave sir? You have a meeting with ALC sir.
请他明天上午过来开会，现在已经很晚了
Request him for a meeting tomorrow morning. It is already very late now.
好的，先生
Okay, sir.
桑迪普？
Sandeep?
什么？
Sorry?
很多像桑迪普这样的人来来往往
So many like Sandeep came and left.
我们已经看这种故事看老了
We have grown older doing all this here.
自己在阳台上看书有可能通过UPSC吗？
Will UPSC get cleared by standing on the terrace and looking into the book?
告诉我，有可能吗？
Tell me will it get cleared?
当考试结果出来时，他们的秘密就会暴露出来
And when the result is out their secrets are revealed.
事情没那么简单
It is not that easy.
许多聪明的人失败了，离开了
Many intelligent ones failed and went away.
你真的得努力学习
You really have to work hard.
这么跟你说吧，阿比拉什
Can I say something, Abhilash?
我可以在你身上看到 UPSC 官员的影子
I can see a UPSC officer in you.
永远不要放弃，好吗
Don't ever give up. Okay.
这是什么？
What is this?
“我的双手似乎空空如也，束手束脚”
"My hands seem to be empty and tied."
“这位隐士遭遇了挫折”
"The recluse has suffered a setback."
“他找不到上帝”
"He could not find God."
“他不能分开”
"He could not stay separated."
“你什么也做不成”
"You could not achieve anything."
“上帝，你的方式有什么奇怪的?”
"What strange way is yours, God?"
“上帝，你为什么要剪断我的梦中风筝?”
"Why did you cut the kite of my dreams, God?"
“直到现在我还很快乐，但是现在我不快乐了，上帝”
"Till now I was happy but now I am not, God."
“这些谈话是虚假的，因为它们唤醒了梦想”
"These talks are false as they awaken dreams."
“他们总是惹麻烦，让我们哭泣”
"They always trouble and makes us cry."
“好像有盏灯熄灭了，伙计”
"As if some lamp got extinguished, buddy."
“他们总是抹去我们的记忆，让我们哭泣”
"They always erase and make us cry."
“一切都变得四分五裂”
"Everything is getting scattered."
“眼泪很重”
"The tears are very heavy."
“大海觉得它们沉重”
"The sea finds them heavy."
“如果我找到了，那么我就会实现它”
"If I find it then I will achieve it."
“我和每个人都断绝了关系”
"I have broken ties with everyone."
（接下来是一段广告）
在非学院学习有多容易？
How easy it is to study on Unacademy?
你明白了吗？
Did you understand properly?
- 是的-很好
- Yes. - Very good.
现在丽卡也可以去 Aanganwadi 了，也可以同时学习了
Now Rekha can go to Aanganwadi also and can study simultaneously.
我不能给你太多时间
I will not be able to give you much time.
我的工作量越来越大了
My workload is increasing.
但是你对 UPSC 的准备不会停止
But your preparation for UPSC will not stop.
我也已经为此做了安排
I have made arrangements for that as well.
我已经订阅了你的个人 Unacademy
I have taken your individual subscription of Unacademy
所以没什么好担心的
so there is nothing to worry about.
您可以加入测试系列的市电
You can join test series of mains.
这里有许多优秀的教育工作者
There are many good educators here.
学习资料在这里，每日计划表也在这里
Study material is there. A daily planner is available.
现场测验也在那里，免费的笔记和其他一切都在那里
Live quizzes are also there. Free notes and everything else is there.
所以没什么好担心的
So there is nothing to worry about.
好吧
Okay.
长官，ALC官员20分钟后到达办公室
Sir, ALC sir is going to reach the office in 20 minutes.
- 我换好衣服就过去-好的，先生
- I'll be there. I'll change and come. - Okay sir.
好吧我走了
Okay. I'll leave.
先生，我的是印地语的
Sir, mine is a Hindi medium.
这里既有印地语也有英语
There is Hindi as well as English here.
所以现在无助可以阻止你学习或成为一个 IAS
So now helplessness can stop you from studying or becoming an IAS.
Unacademy 非常好
Unacademy is very good.
所以现在我们每个星期天都会见面
So now we will meet every Sunday.
好的，先生
Okay, sir.
- 吃完早饭就走-好的
- Have breakfast and go. -
（广告结束）
- 我来谈谈会议的事-哪个会议？
- I will talk about the meeting. - Which meeting?
长官，他是 ALC 的官员，这位是他的下属
Sir, he is ALC sir and he is his subordinate.
晚上好，先生
Good evening sir.
桑迪普兄弟
Brother Sandeep.
苏里亚帕尔，这是我在纳加尔的学长，桑迪普先生
Suryapal, is my senior Mr. Sandeep from Rajinder Nagar.
你好
Hello.
请坐
Please have a seat.
我已经看过邮件，但是根本没想到你就是
I had read the mail but did not have any idea
劳工委员会的桑迪普 · 奥兰
that you are Assistant Labor Commission Sandeep Ohlan.
我只知道你是桑迪普兄弟
I just know you as brother Sandeep.
你真好
So sweet of you.
但我知道那是你的办公室
But I knew that it was your office.
不要太正式
Stop being formal.
你妻子怎么样了？
Tell me how is your wife?
库苏姆？
Kusum?
当然，除了她还有别人吗？
Of course. Is there anyone else other than her?
不，库萨姆和我已经分手了
No, Kusum and I are not together anymore.
离婚？
Divorce?
不，我们没有结婚
No, we never got married.
这是什么意思？
What does that mean?
你没去吗？
Didn't you go?
如果我失败了
If I went after failing
那这四年的时光我拿什么弥补？
then who would have accounted for those four years?
这就是我没去的原因
That is why I did not go.
她为什么要问
Why would she ask
她只是在等你
She was waiting just for you.
她是在等我
She was waiting.
当…
When
我没有通过 UPSC 的时候，我觉得
I did not clear UPSC then I felt
我应该尝试考PCS
I should attempt PCS.
直到我通过了 PCS
Till I cleared PCS
她却不在了
she left.
你必须在生活中做出牺牲
You have to make sacrifices in life.
今天你是一位受人尊敬的公务员
Today you are such a respected civil servant.
无私地为人民服务
You are serving selflessly.
请喝茶
Please have tea.
是的，先生，当然，我是无私奉献
Right, sir. Of course, I am serving selflessly.
长官，当我得知没有通过 UPSC 时
Sir, when I did not clear UPSC
我觉得通过PCS对我的自尊来说是必须的
I felt PCS was a must for my self-respect.
但我错了
But I was wrong.
那不是自尊，而是自我
That was not my self-respect but my ego.
我认为库苏姆等我是理所当然的
I took Kusum for granted.
兄弟，我觉得你当时的所作所为，现在看来是值得的
Brother, I feel what you did at that time is worth it today.
我一直都很崇拜你，我不觉得你错了
I have always idolized and I don't feel you are wrong.
不要通过我来为你的错误开脱
Don't justify your mistakes through me.
我知道你和海莉娅的事
I know what happened between you and Dhairya.
如果你不介意的话，我可以跟你说几句真心话吗？
If you don't mind shall I share something with you?
当然，你说
Yes, sure.
当然
Sure.
告诉我
Tell me.
你知道我的感受吗？
Do you know what I feel?
我感觉自己就像一颗卫星
I feel like a satellite
利用火箭的力量进入到太空轨道
who achieved its orbit in space with the force of a rocket
却忘了火箭的重要性
but forgot the importance of the rocket.
我把火箭扔到了身后
I left it somewhere behind.
我只是在我的轨道上一圈又一圈地独自前进
I just go round and round alone in my orbit.
我对这个世界有帮助
I am of help to the world
却被困在了轨道上
but have got trapped in the axis.
卫星是一个机器，不会被干扰
Satellite is still a machine and it does not bother.
但是如果没有爱的力量，没有人际关系和友谊
But a human is directionless in moving on its axis
人在轨道上前进时，是没有方向的
without the force of love, relationships and friendship.
我们花了很长时间才意识到这一点
We realize it very late
我们是在为国家工作
that we are working for the country
但是没有人为我们感到骄傲
but there is no one to feel proud of us.
人民有时会鼓掌、赞扬我们，有时也会骂我们
People appreciate and applaud and sometimes curse as well.
但是在内心深处，什么都没有
But totally empty from inside. Zero.
没有人和你一起哭笑
There is no one to laugh and cry with you.
库苏姆就是我的火箭
Kusum was my rocket.
为了达到我的高度，我失去了她
I lost her to achieve my heights.
我应该握着她的手，真的
I should have held her hand. Really.
我做到的
I left her.
只有离开了她
I did that.
牺牲你的父母，爱和友谊，来实现你的梦想
Do you know it is not worth to sacrifice
真的不值得
your parents, love and friendship for your dreams.
一点都不值得
Not worth it at all.
你一定知道
You must be aware of
耳朵里的液体可以让人体保持平衡
the fluid in the ear that balances the human body
对我来说库苏姆就是那种液体
and Kusum was that fluid for me.
而这液体已经从我的生活中消失了
The fluid has vanished from my life.
空空如也
Empty.
我很高兴我们能够为国家服务
I am happy that we are able to serve the country.
我们为这个国家做了很多，但是
We are doing a lot for the country but
生命的满足往往就是平衡
the fulfillment of life is the balance.
当我们备考 UPSC 的时候，我们非常困惑
When we were doing UPSC we were very confused
到底应不应该给自己留一条退路
that Plan B should be there or not.
后来我才明白，退路存在的意义，就是保持平衡
The main aim of Plan B is to maintain the balance.
对吧？
Right?
我们太自私了
We were so selfish.
只想着我们自己
We just thought about ourselves.
我们觉得其他人的恐惧、自负和不确定性并不重要
We felt the fears, egos, and uncertainties of others do not have any importance.
我们只是朝着一个方向继续前进
We just kept on going in one direction.
那就是我们的世界
That was our world.
看看我的骄傲
Look at my pride.
我从没向库萨姆道过歉
I never ever apologized to Kusum.
我希望有人能告诉我，指引我
I wish there was someone to tell me, guide me.
我失去了我的机会
I lost my chance.
我永远不能纠正我的错误
I can't amend my mistakes.
对不起
I am sorry.
我先走了
I'll take your leave.
打扰了，先生
Thank you for your time, sir.
再见
Bye.
谢谢你
Thank you.
祝你一切顺利
All the best.
继续前进很容易
It is so easy to keep moving on.
但是只有当我们停下来的时候，一切才会安静下来
Only if we were moving and rest everything was still.
我试着去思考这个有着十个脑袋的毫无意义的世界
I have tried to think about this a senseless world with ten heads
并且试图用20只手去解决问题
and have tried to achieve it with 20 hands.
我让这件事变得非常困难
I have made it very difficult for me.
一开始，每个人都想从头开始
In the beginning, everyone wants to start from the beginning.
但是走到尽头却失去了勇气
But lose courage till they reach the end.
我们对结局不感兴趣
We are not interested in how it ends.
这一切都按照我们的意愿，开始了华丽的表演
That which started with pomp and show as per our wish.
先生，您找我吗？
Sir, did you call me?
苏利帕，通知你的家人
Surypal, inform your family
你接下来的两天都不能回家
that you will not be able to come home for two days.
好吧
Okay.
好的，先生
Fine sir.
翻越艰难的丛林和高山的时候
While accomplishing difficult jungles and high mountains
当你战胜了最后一座山峰
When you win the last peak.
当你觉得没有什么差别的时候
When you feel there is no difference left
在你和那些粗糙的石头之间
between you and the roughness of those stones
你已经赢了
that you have won.
当你的额头承受第一场冰雪风暴
When you will bear the first storm of ice on your forehead
你也不会颤抖
and you will not tremble
然后你会发现赢得一切并没有什么区别
then you will find that there is no difference in winning everything.
直到最后都不要失去希望
And not losing hope till the end.
阿比拉什，阿比拉什..
Abhilash, Abhilash...
好了，大家回去工作吧
Okay, hurry up and finish your work.
谢谢你，先生
Thank you, sir.
阿比拉什，你留下
Abhilash, you stay.
好的，先生
Yes, sir.
你有什么问题吗？
Do you have any problems here?
没有，长官
No, sir.
那你为什么不开心？
Then why aren't you happy?
不，先生，我很高兴
No, sir. I am happy.
不，你回来七个月了
No. It's been seven months since you joined
但你总是很悲伤
but you always remain sad.
还是你觉得公司不认可你的工作？
Or do you feel that company does not recognize your work?
事实上，你是一个优秀的员工
In fact, you are a brilliant employee.
你需要升职吗？
Do you need a promotion?
我都可以，先生
Whatever you say, sir.
也不感兴趣吗
Look, there is no excitement.
不，先生..
No, sir...
那么你可能是因为工作压力太大了
Then maybe you are burnt out because of work.
那我明白了
Now I understand.
去放松一下
Go and chill.
去迪拜
Go to Dubai.
不，先生，那不是... ，谢谢，先生
No, sir that is not...thank you, sir.
不，先生，没有必要的“让我们谈谈时事新闻吧”
No, sir, it is not required. 'Let's move to the news of the hour.'
好吧，如果不去迪拜，那就去马来西亚吧? “ UPSC 给了有志于成为公务员的人一份礼物”
Okay if not to Dubai then Malaysia? 'UPSC has given Civil Services Aspirants a gift.'
“政府已经批准给予6次考试机会”
'Government has given approval to give 6 instead of 4 attempts.'
“歌曲开始播放，悄悄地留在心里”
"The songs started playing that stayed in heart secretly."
“欲望开始在眼睛里暗暗流露”
"The desires started showing secretly in the eyes."
“让空气进入翅膀，赞美肩膀，继续前进... ...”
"Give air to the wings and acclaim the shoulders and move on..."
“给我一个机会，生活”
"Give me an opportunity life"
”我们不害怕问题”
"we are not scared of problems."
”我们已经准备好前进了”
"we are ready to move ahead."
“让我们忘记彼此之间过去的怨言吧”
"Let's forget all the old complaints that we had against each other."
“让我们再次聚在一起，就像我们从未分开过一样”
"Let's all come together again as if we never got separated."
“让我们聚在一起，开开心心的”
"Let's all come together and be happy."
你好
Yes.
我能拿回房间的钥匙吗？
Will I get the keys to the room?
你在工作，对吧？
You were doing a job. Right?
叔叔，我辞职了
Uncle, I left the job.
那你现在要做什么？
What will you do now?
UPSC.